Just so we're clear, people are legitimately supporting the murder of somebody on a train
because they were a homeless person and they were loud.
But let's take it back even further.
When did it become okay to just kill people because you think they should die?
Right. Trayvon Martin, Kyle Rittenhouse, and the BLM protesters.
Ahmaud Arbery's murderers were eventually brought to justice, but not without the DA making it very possible that they got off because she was, of course, colluding.
The thing that is the trend in all of these is Black people as the victims.
And in the case of Kyle Rittenhouse, it wasn't a Black person that was the victim, but they were supporting the lives of Black people as victims.
This vigilantism for the sake of protecting a white America is not new, and it was supported post-antebellum.
So whenever you lie to yourself and say, you know, things aren't that bad, just know that they're going to be if we keep going down this road because that's the goal for them.
So if you're struggling to decide what to do, it'suet they're going to be having a dark woman, fast going down, fast going down, fast going down, fast going down, fast going down one more way.
So I'll now go with thevens look for you guys.
And then finish up trick, straight on the ability to catch.
So I'm not going the wrong person.
Uhmm, to try, I'm not going the wrong person.
So if I'm not going the wrong person, I'm going to transpose it.